export const quiz = {
    topic: 'Javascript',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is CSS ?',
        choices: ['It’s a style sheet language that determines how the elements/contents in the page are looked/shown.', 'Grid framework', 'Web framework', 'Database'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'It’s a style sheet language that determines how the elements/contents in the page are looked/shown.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the Box model in CSS? ',
        choices: ['The CSS Box consists of Width and height (or in the absence of that, default values and the content inside), padding, borders, margin.', 'Element that wide using on html', 'Element on Bootstrap', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'The CSS Box consists of Width and height (or in the absence of that, default values and the content inside), padding, borders, margin.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What are the advantages of using CSS?',
        choices: ['Separation of content from presentation', 'Easy to maintain','Bandwidth', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'Tags are component of the HTML that defines how the content will be structured and  whereas Attributes are used along with the HTML tags to define the characteristics of the element',
      },
      {
        question: 'What are void elements in HTML?',
        choices: ['None of these answers', 'HTML attributes which do not have closing tags', 'HTML elements which do not display on the browser', 'HTML elements which do not have closing tags'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'HTML elements which do not have closing tags',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is not limitation of CSS?',
        choices: ['Browser Compatibility', 'Cross Browser issue', 'Compatible with other programming languages', 'There is no parent selector'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Compatible with other programming languages',
      },      
      {
        question: 'How to include CSS in the webpage ?',
        choices: ['External Style Sheet', 'Embed CSS with a style tag', 'Add inline styles to HTML elements', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },      
      {
        question: 'Which of the answers is a type of Selector in CSS ?',
        choices: ['Class', 'ID', 'A and B', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'A and B',
      },      
      {
        question: 'Which is a CSS frameworks?',
        choices: ['Bootstrap', 'React', 'Node.js','Angular'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Bootstrap',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is meant by RGB stream?',
        choices: ['Selector', 'Element', 'Colors', 'Grid','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Colors',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What is not formating tags in HTML?',
        choices: ['<b>', '<i>', '<big>', '<inl>'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: '<inl>',
      },  
      {
        question: 'How can you target h3 and h2 with the same styling ?',
        choices: ['*{color:red;}', 'h2, h3 {color: red;}', 'h3.{color:red;},h2'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'h2, h3 {color: red;}',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Which is a media type allowed by CSS?',
        choices: ['Audio', 'Grip media','Interactive media','All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What is responsive web design ?',
        choices: ['Design that is compitable for all devices', 'Design that is compitable for reuse', 'Design that is compitable for easy testing'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Design that is compitable for all devices',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Is it important to test the webpage in different browsers ?',
        choices: ['Yes', 'No'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Yes',
      },  
      {
        question: 'How is opacity specified in CSS3?',
        choices: ['It is measured in the range from none to full', 'It is measured in the range from 0% to 100%', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'It is measured in the range from 0% to 100%',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What is common between class and ID ?',
        choices: ['Both class and ID are selectors.', 'File tag and parenthesis', 'Both class and ID are used in HTML to assign a reference from CSS.', 'A and B'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'A and B',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What does !important mean in CSS ?',
        choices: ['The style “!important” in the CSS has the highest precedence.', 'The style “!important” in the CSS has the lowest precedence.', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'The style “!important” in the CSS has the highest precedence.',
      },  
      {
        question: 'How do I restore the default value of a property ?',
        choices: ['Initial', 'Reset', 'None', '*'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Initial',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What is the difference between reset vs normalize CSS ?',
        choices: ['Reset remove all built-in styles and Normalize CSS correct part of the built-in styles', 'Reset correct part of the built-in style and Normalize CSS remove all built-in styles', 'Reset is a part of Normalize'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Reset remove all built-in styles and Normalize CSS correct part of the built-in style',
      },  
      {
        question: 'When does DOM reflow occur ?',
        choices: ['DOM reflow occurs when you insert, remove, and animate the elements', 'DOM reflow occurs when you insert, move, update, remove, and animate the elements', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'DOM reflow occurs when you insert, move, update, remove, and animate the elements',
      },  
    ],
  };
  